Overcomer Emiator

A passionate Programmer

Benin City

xceldeveloper@gmail.com

+2348158696460

Hi, I am a passionate developer with good experience designing Webapps, Blogs, Android Apps, Opensource Projects etc utilizing varieties of Software Technologies which include Vuejs, Nuxt, Flutter, Nodejs, Django, JQuery, Tailwindcss, Scss, Git

I have experience working remotely building meaningful and productive software with also the ability to work with minimal supervision as I have the zeal to tackle any problems I might encounter independently to achieve the desired result.

Work Experience

Frontend Developer

Scelloo - Lagos February 2021 to Present

Frontend Developer at Scelloo (SaaS Company) exercising my Vuejs and Tailwindcss skills in building its Software

Per time Frontend Developer

2GFields - Benin April 2020 to Present

Per time Developer at 2GFields (Software Company) as a Frontend Developer working on Pord

Tech Intern

Ambrose Alli University ICT Depertment - Benin August 2019 to December 2019

Intern at The Department of Information and Telecommunication Ambrose Alli University for a period of 6 months

Education

Undergraduate in Mathematics

University of Benin - Nigeria October 2016 to August 2021

Skills

- JavaScript (4 years)
- JQuery (3 years)
- Java (2 years)

- Vuejs (2 years)
- Nuxtjs (2 years)
- Nodejs (1 year)
- Kotlin (1 year)
- Tailwindcss (1 year)
- Django (1 year)
- Git (1 year)
- SCSS (Less than 1 year)

Languages

• English - Fluent

Links

http://linkedin.com/in/overcomer-emiator-5573141b2/

https://github.com/xceldeveloper

https://twitter.com/xceldeveloper

https://xceldeveloper.com

Publications

vue-device-detector-js

https://www.npmjs.com/package/vue-device-detector-js January 2021

A vuejs plugin for the client device detection

vue-theme-manager

https://www.npmjs.com/package/vue-theme-manager

March 2021

A vuejs plugin for Managing theme(s) colors in the whole of your Vue web app. It has support for Vue 2 and Vue 3